Hello.
- Hello.
- Where are we?
- We are in Isaberg, in Småland.
Yes.
- And what do you see behind, then?
- Our house and dad, which packs his backpack.
Isaberg is a ski slope in the winter.
And now in the summer you can do lots of fun action activities here.
Very cool!
We came here yesterday and then it was full of mountain bikers everywhere.
You can go up to the top and cycle down.
We should not.
- I can't.
- No I know.
We start the day at high altitude.
- Camera mounting in progress.
- Yeah.
Thanks, Alma.
How nice.
- Are you nervous?
- No.
- It's pretty high.
- It will be great fun.
- How professional they look.
- Right?
It looks like they are going up and folding trees or pulling electricity into any post, or something.
- Daddy, when do you put on your suit?
- Soon.
- We are ready!
- Yes!
Yes, yes, yes I have the coolest suit, wow!
I got a green helmet because I have the world's biggest head, so now I really look like a watermelon.
- Are these the steps to climb up?
- Right?
Worst watermelon.
We will have a review now, Harry.
The one that is like a C is open and the one that is like a U is closed.
Now I have one that is open, and then I can't unlock the other.
It only goes halfway.
So you are always stuck up there.
The arrow against the magnet, and press firmly.
Then you see that it is also locked, and then you will get rid of the other.
Press the button and pull it against the wire.
You don't have to use your fingers.
So, then it unlocks.
(Harry) pull up and pull down, pull up and pull down ...
Oh, I happened to hit the camera.
(Alma) Harry, stop now.
- Oh, someone is a little taken over.
- Yes ... we'll see how it goes, this.
Now Harry will try.
♪ Prince Ali, which magic, aliababa ♪
It feels like I'm too heavy and will fall down.
Help, oh, help!
Now I'm going to skip to the next.
It's ... half -hard to go and film ...
But what do we do because you get to hook at home.
What do you think of the high altitude track?
- Great fun!
- Perfect!
- Very funny.
- It was really fun.
And really warm!
Yes, extremely hot.
We had to go in and sit down and have lunch.
Usually, like Swedish, you always sit outside when the weather is nice, but it is almost too hot.
I know you can't say so, but yes ...
Yes, Alma got almost a little sunbathing there for a while.
Now we will test something we have never tested before, but which at least I am very embarrassed.
What do you feel?
Me too!
- I'm really nice.
- Rodel!
Yes, Rodel!
Summer rod.
The track is there.
I turn the camera.
- There.
- Woho!
Are you really that?
"Forbidden to stop", "accelerate" it says.
- The rowing was absolutely insanely funny.
- Super fun.
- It felt, in the curves, like you would fly out.
- Yes, it did.
So it was a creepy moment in that.
So, it was a curve that I never really dared to keep full skewers in.
- Full gas.
- Yes, full gas.
It was a bit jerky, actually.
It's fun that there is so much action here.
I get some new Zealand vibes.
Yes indeed!
A little rotorua ...
Yes!
So here it was in New Zealand - nature place and lots of action you could do.
- mm, this ... swing.
- Yes exactly.
- We just test a few things here, there is much more.
- (Harry) Wieee, I go cable car, wieee ...
- Golf, all the Mountain Bike tracks, and so on.
- Yes.
Of course.
This is the last stop on our Småland trip that we do in collaboration with Visit Småland.
All our stops are on a link in the descriptive text,-
-If you are curious about any of the places we visited in these four vlogs.
- Yes.
Yes.
- So check it out if you want.
Check out.
- "Yes."
"Check it out."
This is how we live.
Here is Mom and Dad's room.
Here is the living room.
- And an upside down Harry.
- Yes.
And here is the kitchen, and ...
Here is mine and Harry's room.
- You can excuse the mess.
We are on vacation.
- Yes.
Excuse us.
- And the technology has moved from bed to the kitchen table.
- Yes.
So here it is sometimes.
Here comes the camera Christmas tree.
It fits, because we are in a mountain cabin.
Yes, but exactly.
Yes exactly.
This must have been a mountain cabin from the beginning.
And then this ski resort, as it was from the beginning, has redone and become a little more summery.
- They also run skis here, when there is snow.
- Yes exactly.
When it's snow, yes.
A great facility, I must say.
I like it.
Nice with a lake nearby.
God, what a nice.
It's super nice.
We are on this awesome sauna raft.
Oh!
What a light.
So, it's still so hot.
It is six o'clock in the evening.
In there, Alma sits, and cozy.
With a camera!
Should you jump in with that one?
(Harry) Oh!
You splash!
It was a little cold on your feet.
It was a little cold on your feet ...
- Was it?
- ... at the bottom, so I got a little ...
What a pillemary mine you did.
Oh, now you made the castle minute.
Show for mom.
- "in said no."
(I said no) - "You Said No?"
(You said no?)
(Harry) This is going to be jerky.
I thought we could take care and summarize Småland, instead of today's question.
Yes.
Beautiful, I think.
Really beautiful.
- Yes.
Much to do.
- Very much to do.
For family, top.
And we say that from the heart, that is.
Many lovely bathing lakes.
A lot of coffee, everywhere.
Yes, they love coffee and sugar!
We have not filmed that much, but it is like coffee cottages, waffles, ice cream, pastries and sweets everywhere.
Mixed with flea markets and small towns.
And knob.
Yes, now it is extremely bump.
I try to stand still, but my whole body just wants to ...
Thanks for watching this video!
Feel free to leave a thumbs up, or down.
Comment, ask questions and have a great summer, and we will see you again soon!